Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers - Photographs
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Lamar Alexander Photograph Collection
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0734.2
21.42 linear_feet
- Series I: Governor’s Papers
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Campaign, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Campaign, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Campaign, Walk Across Tennessee, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Campaign, Walk Across Tennessee, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Campaign, Walk Across Tennessee, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Campaign, Family Homes During Walk, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Meeting in Memphis with A. Saeki, President of Sharp Corporation, December 1978 (Box 1)
    - Unknown Event, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Inaugural Ceremonies, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Inauguration, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Inauguration and Reception, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Cabinet Meeting, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Budget Message, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Commission, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Chattanooga Trip, 1979 (Box 1)
    - State Dinner, May 4, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Christmas, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Christmas, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Christmas 1979, Original negatives (Box 1)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Governor Alexander in Office with People, January 7, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Legislature, January 8, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Small Business Meeting, February 13, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Flying Canadian Flag over the Tennessee Capitol, February 15, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Roane County Sheriff, February 17, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Proclamations, March 4, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Proclamations, H. Lowe, March 18, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Groundbreaking, Bill Signings, Visitors, R. Hood, March 19, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Gospel Music Proclamation, March 20, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Students in Front of Legislative Plaza, March 26, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Members of Carter County Historical Society; Pickett County Girls Basketball Team, March 27, 1980 (Box 2)
    - 4-H Club, April 1980 (Box 2)
    - Proclamations, April 1, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Wayne County Group, April 2, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Governor’s Prayer Breakfast, April 3, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Dogwood Festival, Knoxville, April 11, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Mule Day, Columbia, April 12, 1980 (Box 2)
    - State of the State Address, April 14, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Bill Signings; MDA Poster Child; GOP Women, April 15, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Teenage Republicans; Children at Pool, April 16, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Bill Signing HB 2491/SB 2423 (TN Prison Agri-Industries), April 18, 1980 (Box 2)
    - (2 Folders) Century III Celebration; Elks National Youth Week, April 24, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Republican Women at Residence, April 29, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Presentation of Portrait; Bill Signing, April 30, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Presentation of Walking Stick; Judge James Thompson, May 5, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Representative Paul Starnes and Signing of HB2325/SB2287 (Health Care Bill); Senator Buzz Elkins and Byrd Duncan, May 7, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Republican Women, May 13, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Tennessee River Four-County Port Authority Signing Ceremony; Signing of Tax Incentives Law; Ensworth School Students, May 14, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Black Leaders, Small Business, May 15, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Commissioner Sansom’s Children’s Classes, May 16, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Governor Alexander Meets with Newly Appointed Directors of the Tennessee Housing Development Agency; Proclamations, May 20, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Small Business Administration, May 22, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Swearing in of New Members of the Occupational Health and Safety Review Commission, May 27, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Governor Alexander with Group of People, June 2-3, 1980 (Box 2)
    - President’s Conference on Families, June 6, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Kenneth Wood, Walk-a-Thon Man, June 9, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Nigerian Delegation; Presentation to the Governor; Proclamations, June 10, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Tennessee Judicial Conference, June 11, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Miss Tennessee National Teenager, June 13, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Tennessee’s Miss LaPetite; Bowater Southern Paper Corporation, June 23, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Capitol Club Group, July 2, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Swearing in of Arzo Carson, Director of Tennessee Bureau of Investigation; Return of State’s Official Scales Ceremony, July 8, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Herb Luntz, July 10, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Gatlinburg Place, July 11, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Presentation of Baxter Taylor Papers; Proclamations, July 29, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Erwin Baseball, Representative Whitson, August 4, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Swearing in of Ray Whitley, District Attorney General; Polk County Officials; Employee Suggestion Awards; Energy Conservation Month, Tennessee Energy Authority, August 28, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Judge Ed Williams; Mayor Gene Record, September 5, 1980 (Box 2)
    - IMPAC Representatives; Runner-Up Little Miss Tennessee Pageant, September 23, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Governor Alexander with Pedro Paz; Governor Alexander with Group of People, September 24, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Genealogy Presentation, September 29, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Foreign Trade Seminar; Presentation of Christmas Seals, September 30, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - (Contact Sheets), October 7, 1980 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), October 9, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Dr. Harry Gilmore and Lambuth College Supporters, October 20, 1980 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), October 27, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Nissan Announcement, October 30, 1980 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), November 7, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Boys’ Club; License Plate Presentation, November 13-14, 1980 (Box 3)
    - John Parish, November 26, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Floyd Cramer; Church Women United Sunday; Civil Air Patrol Week, December 3, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Future Farmers of America; John Walton West, December 9, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Phi Delta Kappa Week; Outstanding Achievement Awards; DHS Service Awards, December 22, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Budget Message, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Three New Commissioner Ceremonies: Parker Etherage, Jr. (Tourist Development), Dr. Robert McElrath (Department of Education), Charles Howell (Department of Conservation), January 5, 1981 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), January 9, 1981 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), January 12, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Rep. Bill Carter, Representative Mike Robertson, Representative Larry Huskey, January 13, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Jump Rope for Heart; Department of Employment Security, January 16, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Miss Continental Tennessee; Fisk UNCF Telethon Day, January 27, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Charles McMillan, Captain Charles T. McMillan II Proclamation, January 29, 1981 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), February 2, 1981 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), February 6, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Representative Rufus Jones, Shelby County, February 11, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Boy Scouts; Lenoir City Students, February 12, 1981 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), February 16, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Presentation Handicapped/Disabled Awards; Presentation of Painting to Alexander, February 17, 1981 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), February 25, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Randy McNally, Sharon Bell, February 26, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Foreign Language Week, February 27, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Women’s History Week; Beta Sigma Phi; Agriculture Day; Employ the Older Worker Week, March 3, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Senator Hamilton’s Pages, March 5, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Union City Students, March 6, 1981 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), March 10, 1981 (Box 3)
    - John Parish, Nancy Wade, Representative Lowe, March 11, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Bob Knestrick and Class (St. Paul’s Christian Academy), March 12, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Etowah Head Hunters; Mayo Wix, Representative Clark, March 15, 1981 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), March 18, 1981 (Box 3)
    - World’s Fair; Reverend Mull; Lamar Alexander at Piano; Presentation of Portrait, March 19, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Counsel General of Mexico, March 24, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Ned Ray McWherter; Representative Steve Bivens, March 25, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Sacred Heart School; Future Farmers of America; Victor Ashe and Bob Rial, March 26, 1981 (Box 3)
    - (Contact Sheets), March 27, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Miss Tennessee USA; Cinderella Girls, Presentation of Tennessee Conservationist Magazine, March 31, 1981 (Box 3)
    - David Green, WGNS Radio-Murfreesboro; Signing of SB 26 (Child Restraint), April 1, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Signing of SB 124 (Wage Assignment), April 8, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Senator Victor Ashe and Students, April 9, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Dogwood Arts Festival, April 10, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Signing of Contracts with China to buy Tennessee Agriculture Products, April 13, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Miss Tennessee Week; Sudekum Kids; Cub Scouts; Governor’s Trophy Match; Industry Appreciation Month, April 15, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Sporting Event, April 16, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Proclamation Signing with Charlie Daniels; Signing of SB 918/HB 651 (Synthetic Fuels) and SB 758/HB 1000 (Energy Authority); Signing of HJR 77 Honoring Oak Ridge High School Football Team, April 21, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Signing of HB 1027 and HB 719 (Hazardous Materials and Scenic Highways); High School Students, April 22, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Cookbook Presentation; Louisville School History Class, April 23, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Senator Victor Ashe and 4th Grade Class from Blount County; Proclamations, April 29, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Gerald Ford Visit, April 30, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Legislative Interns, May 4, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Representative Hillis; Dr. Oike (Hirosaki University) and Dr. Eisterhold (University of Tennessee), May 5, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Randy McNally Bill Signing, May 6, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Carter Middle School; Bud Lawrence (President of American Gas Association), May 7, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Humboldt Strawberry Festival Parade; Governor’s Luncheon, May 8, 1981 (Box 4)
    - (Contact Sheets), May 11, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Bill Signing; Proclamations; Ryszard Frelek, Ambassador of Poland to the United Nations, May 13, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Student Group; State Property, May 14, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Kick-off of Let’s Go Tennesseeing Campaign, May 18, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Signing of SB 656/HB 688; Luncheon, May 20, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Proclamations, May 26, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Ralph Duncan, May 27, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Ben Longley, Joe Paul Good, Curtis Hampton in Governor’s Office, May 28, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Wearwood Elementary School, Meet with Residents of Greenback, June 2, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Governor’s Address to Giles County High School Graduation, June 4, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Francis Guess, Mr. and Mrs. John Roberts, June 8, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Presentation of Cake with 40 Trees; Fraternal Week; Bill Signing, June 9, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Hee Haw Taping, Minnie Pearl, June 10, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Governor Alexander Presents Service Awards and Visits with Department of Transportation Employees, June 12, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Mrs. W.W. Fisher (Lamar Alexander’s Aunt) and Emily Caldwell; Presentation of Plaque, June 15, 1981 (Box 4)
    - (Contact Sheet), June 16, 1981 (Box 4)
    - House of God, Ribbon Cutting for New Sanctuary; Tennessee State Museum; Greeneville Room Luncheon; Editorial Cartoonists; Bill Signings, June 17, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Sewanee, June 21, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Needlepoint People from Memphis, June 27, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Swearing in of Julia Gibbons, June 30, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Swearing in of Bill Sansom, Bob Farris, Darrell Akins, Bill Koch and Martha Warfield, July 1, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Pops Concert in the Park with the Chattanooga Symphony, Lamar Alexander Playing Piano, July 4, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Hazel Curtis (Lamar Alexander’s Cousin), July 8, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Minnie Pearl and Roy Acuff; Welcome Wagon and Ladies, July 9, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Representative Bill Owens; JC Members; Marie Collins and Grandchildren, July 21, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Francis Guess, W.C. Sheffield, July 23, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Maryville Little League All Stars, July 30, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Lamar Alexander with Kingsport Fun Fest T-Shirt, August 3, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Safe Growth Action Team; Jim Harrison and wife Nelda, August 4, 1981 (Box 4)
    - (Contact Sheet), August 5, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Swearing in of Norma Crow, September 1, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Robert L. McElrath and Doyle Gains, September 2, 1981 (Box 4)
    - (Contact Sheets), September 10, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Lambda Chi Alpha, September 11, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Roy Acuff Roast and Toast, September 20, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Proclamations, September 22, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Bill Sansom et al., Certificate of Conformance in Financial Reporting; General Carl Wallace, FEMA Director; Roy Acuff Taping, September 23, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Weigh Station; Band at Fair, September 28, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Charlie Daniels Presents Christmas Seals; Korean Council General Dong Woon Chu, September 29, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Governor’s Three Star Award Presented to Hohenwald Officials, October 1, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Jonesboro, October 2, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Economic Community Development Employees; Beauty Teen Scholarship Winners; Proclamations; Winner of Dairy Awards, October 6, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Greyhound Bus and Officials; Charles Howell and Staff; YMCA Youth in Government, October 8, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Hunter Van Pelt; The Sparta Expositor Newspaper Clippings, October 9, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Yorktown Commemoration, October 13, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Executives from the US Security Fire and Casualty Insurance Company, October 14, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Recognition Award for James Coe; Dick Grant, Head of Boeing in Oak Ridge; Elmo Williams, Producer of Gettysburg, October 15, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Commissioner Parker Etherage, Tourism, October 16, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Proclamations; Service Awards, October 20, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Teacher of the Year Presentation; Martha Olsen Award, October 26, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Headshots of Ben Smith (Safe Growth Action Team), October 29, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Lamar Alexander, Mildred Johnson, and Commissioner of Labor Jack Richesin; Midway High School; Biltmore Restaurant Luncheon; Union City; Obion Central High School Assembly, October 30, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Today Show with Willard Scott; Centennial Park; Playing Piano, November 3, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Alex Haley and Parker Etherage; Dinner and Cocktails; Alexander’s Good Time Review, November 4-5, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Dr. Zeman of Czechoslovakia and Representatives of Washington Industries, November 9, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Jake Butcher and S.H. “Bo” Roberts, Jr. meet with Alexander to discuss World’s Fair; League of Women Voters; Youth Appreciation Week, November 10, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Lamar Alexander and Veteran’s Affair Commissioner William (Dusty) Roden, Jr. lead a Veteran’s Day Parade, November 11, 1981 (Box 5)
    - (Contact Sheet), November 25, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Tennessee’s State Christmas Tree; Senator Bob Burleson and Lamar Alexander; Family Photos with Christmas Tree, December 1-2, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Lamar Alexander Welcomes Officials from Pelikan AG; Federation of Republican Women, December 3, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Service Awards, December 7, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Tennessee Farm Bureau Federation, December 8, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Carter Witt, Will Scott, and Richard Klasen (Ford Motor Company), December 10, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Johnny Cash, December 11, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Christmas Taping; Employee Suggestion Awards; Proclamations, December 14, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Choir at Capitol, December 16, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Grady Rhoden and Bob Mason, December 18, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Senator Hugh Scott, Kathleen Carpenter, and Don Mintmire, December 21, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Dining Service, December 22, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Parish Party, December 1981 (Box 5)
    - Will and Jennifer as children, Unknown Date 1981 (Box 5)
    - Paul Summers and Bill Koch, January 4, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Brian T. Hill (Vanderbilt), Sue Pedigo (Volunteer State Community College), Dan Miller (UT Center for Health and Sciences, Memphis – Financial Aid Awareness Week, January 12, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Nissan’s First Supplier, Hoover Universal Inc., January 19, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Family Courts Proposed, Senator William Ortwein and Senator Curtis Person, January 21, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Unknown Speech, January 22, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Charlie Daniels; TRW Officials, January 27, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Metro Center Silver Cup Presentation, January 28, 1982 (Box 5)
    - (Contact Sheets), January 29, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Memphis, Melrose High School; Bishop Effrum, January 30, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Budget Address, Lamar Alexander, Ned Ray McWherter and John Wilder, February 1, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Press Conference, February 3, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Service Awards Presentations, February 4, 1982 (Box 5)
    - (Contact Sheet), February 8, 1982 (Box 5)
    - (Contact Sheets), February 9, 1982 (Box 5)
    - (Contact Sheets), February 10, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Nissan, February 12, 1982 (Box 6)
    - (7 Folders) Forum with Japan on US/Japan Relations, Hyatt Regency Hotel, Nashville; Forum Luncheon; Panel Discussion with Bill Brock, Howard Baker, Mike Mansfield and Yoshio Okawara; Tour of Nissan Plant; Student Study Program with Japan; Bridgestone Tire Announcement, February 13, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Rocky Top Named Official State Song Celebration, Lamar Alexander at Piano, February 15, 1982 (Box 6)
    - (Contact Sheet), February 17, 1982 (Box 6)
    - (2 Folders) Rocky Top Song Celebration; Senator Carl Moore presents copy of “Arts and the States” to Governor Alexander; Forrest School Students, February 18, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Trevor Gatty, British Council General; Carter County Lincoln Day Dinner; Elizabethton, February 19, 1982 (Box 6)
    - William Bringham Presents Gov. Alexander with Sigma Chi Award; Proclamations, February 24, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Senator Hamilton, February 28, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Joe Rodgers; Swearing in of Judge Rose Cantrell, March 1, 1982 (Box 6)
    - C.B. Robinson, March 2, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Howard McNeese and Brainerd School; Governor Alexander with Two Girl Scouts, March 3, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Reverend Eddie Fox, Gentry Crowell and 23 Missionaries; Victor Ashe, Mrs. Robert DeLozier, Mrs. Al Schmutzer and children, March 4-5, 1982 (Box 6)
    - (3 Folders) Composites of Lamar Alexander, State of the State (with McWherter and Wilder), Working in Office, Walking up Capitol Steps, March 8, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Dresden Elementary School; Jim Henry and Jacksboro Jr. High School, March 10, 1982 (Box 6)
    - (3 Folders) President Ronald Reagan Visit, President Reagan in House Chamber, Reception; Speaker McWherter’s Group, March 15, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Agriculture Day with Commissioner Walker, Representative Roscoe Pickering, Representative Ruth Robinson, James Putnam (Tennessee Farm Bureau), and W.W. Armistead (University of Tennessee); Proclamations; Signing of SB 222/HB 140 (Mental Health Contracting), March 16, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Rockwood Jr. High School; George Kelly (East Tennessee State University) and Students; Red Boiling Springs School, March 17, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Swearing in of John L. Parish as Commissioner of the Dept. of Economic and Community Development, March 23, 1982 (Box 6)
    - (2 Folders) Lamar Alexander and Big Bird; Victor Ashe and Lookout Elementary School; Campfire Girls; Signing of HB 1350/SB 1412 (St. Jude), March 24, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Goodpasture 4th Grade Students; Middlesettlements Elementary School Students, March 25, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Tommy Milam and Interns; Tourism, Follow Me To Tennessee Bus, March 26, 1982 (Box 6)
    - (Contact Sheet), March 30, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Clarksville Academy Political Science Class; School Choir; Senator Leonard Dunavant and Interns, March 31, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Proclamations; Highland Rim Elementary School, April 1, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Fiddler Curly Fox and Presentation of HJR 288, April 2, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Easter Bunny and Easter Egg Hunt at the Residence, April 3, 1982 (Box 7)
    - 4-H Club Officers; 35th Annual 4-H Congress; West End Kindergarten Class (Nashville), April 6, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Creation of the Tellico Reservoir Development Agency; Lambuth College Political Science Students; Columbia State Community College Government Students, April 7, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Cast of Celebrities Singing Anti-Litter Campaign Jingles, includes Lamar Alexander, John Wilder, Minnie Pearl, Roy Acuff, and Ned McWherter; Bill Signing; Ripley Elementary School, April 8, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Proclamations, April 13, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Signing of HB 388/SB 535 (Adoption Information), April 15, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Goodyear Top 10 Club; Tennessee Twirling Institute, April 16, 1982 (Box 7)
    - (2 Folders) Honey Alexander talks about Alcohol Abuse Prevention, News Conference; Lunch with Honey Alexander and Alex Haley; Long Hunters; Oakland High School Government Class; Employee Awards, April 21, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Obion Forked Deer Bill Signing; Natural Gas Car, April 22, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Insurance Bill Signing, April 23, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Legislation Signed to Create 2,300-Mile Tennessee Parkway System; Scales Elementary School; Veterans Group Reception, April 27, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Signing and Press Conference Judge Sentencing Bill, April 28, 1982 (Box 7)
    - DUI Bill Signing and Press Conference, April 29, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Paris Fish Fry; Knoxville, World’s Fair Site; State of Tennessee Show, April 30, 1982 (Box 7)
    - World’s Fair Remarks and Dedication Ceremony, US Pavilion, Senator Baker, President Reagan, Tennis Match, May 1, 1982 (Box 7)
    - World’s Fair Ceremony, Senator Baker, President Reagan and Nancy Reagan, May 2, 1982 (Box 7)
    - (2 Folders) 54th Tennessee Future Farmers of America Convention; Jobs for High School Graduates Awards Ceremony, May 3, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Blind Workshop Bill Signing; Representative Carl Moore; Representative Bob Davis, May 6, 1982 (Box 7)
    - 45th Annual West Tennessee Strawberry Festival Parade, Mayor Thomas McCaslin, Reception, May 7, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Announcement of Kroger’s Discount Program, May 11, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Special Legislative Session at World’s Fair; Reception; Doyle High School Assembly, May 12, 1982 (Box 7)
    - High Blood Pressure Month, Governor Alexander gets Blood Pressure Checked; Proclamations, May 19, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Discussing Ideas for Roast of Joe Rodgers, May 20, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Job Skills Survey Announcement; Adult Education Meeting, Knoxville, May 25, 1982 (Box 7)
    - (Contact Sheet), May 26, 1982 (Box 7)
    - 2nd Annual Tennessee World Trade Conference, May 27, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Memphis in May, Sunset Symphony (Large Color Photo), May 30, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - K.Q. Chedester, Bill Goddard, Keel Hunt, June 8, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Preview of Posters for The Vietnam Veterans Leadership Program; Proclamations, June 9, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Tennessee Scenic Parkway Tour, June 10, 1982 (Box 8)
    - (Contact Sheets), June 11, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Raymond Thomason; Proclamations; Governor’s Trophy Match Winners, June 16, 1982 (Box 8)
    - 4-H Club Book Presentation; Richard Lewis, Member of the Board of Regents, June 24, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Appellate Court Appointees, Alan E. Highers and Frank Crawford; Nashville Vocational Technical School Matt Lynch Campus Dedication, June 29, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Tennessee School Food Service Association Convention, June 30, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Ribbon Cutting Ceremony for U.S. Tobacco Museum; Morris Werthan, July 1, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Lamar Alexander Birthday Celebration, July 2, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Memphis Mud Island Grand Opening, July 3, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Lamar Alexander Confers with Advisors about Sequoyah Nuclear Power Plant; Camp Shelby, Hagler Army Aviation, July 8, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Camp Shelby, Tennessee National Guard Four Mile Walk, July 8, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Lamar Alexander at Desk, July 9, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Japanese Dignitaries, July 12, 1982 (Box 8)